For you it's a bit like you
Forgive me, take another option
I won't come back here, I don't want to give you an exception
So much that I gave you the champion
When I needed you, you saw your worst version
Sorry baby, a while ago
That I saw you because of that cat
A wolf like me is not for everyone
A wolf like me is not for you like you
For you like you
For you it's a bit like you
This is to make you more sick
More sick, more sick
I won't come back here, I don't want to cry
I won't come back here, I don't want to give you an exception
So much that I gave you the champion
Sorry baby, a while ago
That I saw you because of that cat
A wolf like me is not for you like you
For you it's a bit like you
Clearly it's more like you
For you it's a bit different
That is why you're with an equal photo
I love you a lot, I too love you
You won't come back here, I won't come back here
I won't come back here, I don't want to cry
I don't even know what happened to you
You're so weird that I don't even distinguish you
I walk by 2 of 22
You changed a Ferrari for a Twingo
You changed a Rolex for a Casio
You're going to be a high school student
Ah, a lot of gym
But I also work a little bit of my brain
How much do you owe me?
Here I feel full
For me everything is fine
I take care of you tomorrow
And if you want to bring her to you, come too
She has a person name
Good
It's not how it sounds to me
It's not a good person name
And a student like me is no longer for you
Like you
For you, like you
For you it's getting bigger
And that's why you're with a little igualita
Like you
For you it's getting bigger
And that's why you're with a little igualita
Like you
That's it, bye