Mr. Blue, I told you that I love you, please believe me
Mr. Blue, I have to go now darling, don't be angry
Know that you're tired, know that you're sore and sick and sad for some reason
So I'll leave you with a smile, kiss you on the cheek and you will call it treason
Mr. Blue, don't hold your head so low that you can't see the sky
Mr. Blue, it ain't so long since you were flying high
That's the way it goes some days, a fever comes at you without a warning
I can see it in your face, you've been waiting to break since you woke up this morning
Mr. Blue, don't hold your head so low that you can't see the sky
Mr. Blue, it ain't so long since you were flying high
Mr. Blue, Mr. Blue
Mr. Blue, I told you that I love you, please believe me